Guide to the Francis P. Squibb Papers 1894-2003
University of Chicago Library
Squibb, Francis P. Papers
1894-2003
16.5 linear feet (18 boxes)
Hanna Holborn Gray Special Collections Research Center University of Chicago Library 1100 East 57th Street Chicago, Illinois 60637 U.S.A.
Francis P. Squibb, jazz musician, curator, and writer. The Francis P. Squibb Papers contain advertisements, articles, correspondence, interviews, photographs, songbooks, fake books, method books, programs, publications, liner notes, record catalogs and discographies, essays, and manuscripts. There is handwritten, printed, and photocopied music as well as music transcriptions.
Information on Use
Access
The collection is open for research.
Biographical Note
Francis P. Squibb was born July 20, 1927 in Brookline, MA. He earned his B.A. in Philosophy from Dartmouth College and a M.A. in Social Philosophy from the University of Illinois. After serving two years in the U.S. Army, Squibb became a jazz musician in the Chicago area.
From 1952-1954, Squibb edited and prepared jazz records for William Russell in Chicago. He then worked for the American Peoples Encyclopedia from 1954-1964. During his tenure as the chief editor at the University of Alabama Press from 1965-1980, he published Storyville, New Orleans by Al Rose. His continued interest in jazz led him to serve as a curator at the William Ransom Hogan Archives of New Orleans Jazz at Tulane University from 1965-1980.
Squibb also wrote liner notes for jazz recordings including Montego Joe’s “Arriba! Con Montego Joe,” Jimmy Witherspoon’s “Evenin’ Blues,” and Shirley Scott’s “Soul Shoutin’.”
Squibb died September 1, 2003 in Flossmoor, IL.
Scope Note
The Francis P. Squibb Papers are divided into four series: Series I, Personal; Series II, Catalogs, Discographies, and Publications; Series III, Printed and Handwritten Music; Series IV, Oversize. The Francis P. Squibb Papers contain advertisements, articles, correspondence, interviews, photographs, songbooks, fake books, method books, programs, publications, liner notes, record catalogs and discographies, essays, and manuscripts. There is handwritten, printed, and photocopied music as well as music transcriptions.
Series I, Personal, contains advertisements, correspondence, interviews, ephemera about musicians, photographs, programs, and drafts of manuscripts written by others. There are advertisements for the jazz club Red Arrow, “Louisiana” brand canned shrimp and okra, and LP record labels. The manuscript “Black Jazz on the Barbary Coast” also contains photographs of musicians. The manuscript, “Louisiana’s Singing Century” is divided into two copies: a complete photocopy in draft form and a complete photocopy with handwritten notes. There is correspondence to Squibb from Eugene Kramer and Mike Hazelnine. The correspondence not addressed to Squibb consists mostly of photocopied letters to and from musicians. The photocopied interviews are with Mrs. Francis Oliver, Ferdinand “Jelly Roll” Morton, Roy Carew, and William Russell. Also included is a music lesson journal.
Series II, Catalogs, Discographies, and Publications, contains record catalogs, discographies, and jazz publications. Publications include Down Beat, Jazz Journal, Jazz World, Record Research, Giants of Jazz, Index of Jazz, and Climax. See Series IV for additional publications.
Series III, Printed and Handwritten Music, contains printed, published, and handwritten music. As received from Squibb, folders are grouped by musician, composer, or style and are arranged alphabetically by subject and alphabetically by title within each subject. Songbooks are listed last. Sheet music is documented by title, lyricist, composer, publisher, and date. Method books and fake books are transcribed and edited mostly for piano. The handwritten music includes composers such as Eubie Blake, Buck Clayton and Don Ewell. Music transcriptions are of Don Ewell and Don Lambert and consist of piano arrangements. Photocopied music includes music by Ferdinand “Jelly Roll” Morton, Scott Joplin, James Scott, and Jess Stacy.
Series IV, Oversize, contains liner notes written by Squibb as well as articles features in Down Beat written by Sharon Pease. There are publications including Metronome and Esquire’s Jazz Book. Residential and business maps outlining areas of Chicago are included.
Related Resources
The following related resources are located in the Department of Special Collections:
http://www.lib.uchicago.edu/e/spcl/select.html
Chicago Jazz Archive
John Steiner. Collection
Subject Headings
Squibb, Francis P.; Carew, Roy; Morton, Jelly Roll, d. 1941; Chicago Defender; Chicago Whip; Jazz -- History and Criticism; Jazz -- Discography; Jazz Musicians -- United States; Jazz -- Periodicals; Piano music; Songs; University of Chicago. Chicago Jazz Archive
INVENTORY
- Series I: Personal
  - Advertisements, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Bunk Johnson, 1939-1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Bunk Johnson, 1939-1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Don Ewell and William Russell, 1945-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Eugene Kramer to Squibb, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Ferdinand "Jelly Roll" Morton and Roy Carew, 1938-1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Ferdinand "Jelly Roll" Morton and Roy Carew, 1938-1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Ferdinand "Jelly Roll" Morton and Roy Carew, 1938-1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Ferdinand "Jelly Roll" Morton and Roy Carew, 1938-1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Ferdinand "Jelly Roll" Morton and Roy Carew, 1938-1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Mike Hazelnine to Squibb, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Interview, Mrs. Francis Oliver, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Interview, Ferdinand "Jelly Roll" Morton, 1938-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Interview, Roy Carew, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Interview, William Russell, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lesson Journal, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript, "Black Jazz on the Barbary Coast," Tom Stoddard, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript, "Black Jazz on the Barbary Coast," Tom Stoddard, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript, "A Chronological Survey of the Chicago Defender and the Chicago Whip from 1909-1930 on the Development of Jazz Music on Chicago's South Side," John Steiner and Charles Sengstock, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript, "A Chronological Survey of the Chicago Defender and the Chicago Whip from 1909-1930 on the Development of Jazz Music on Chicago's South Side," John Steiner and Charles Sengstock, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript, "Louisiana's Singing Century: One Hundred Years of Popular Culture Mirrored in Music," Vaughn L. Glasgow, Al Rose, and Diana Beals Rose, Draft, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript, "Louisiana's Singing Century: One Hundred Years of Popular Culture Mirrored in Music," Vaughn L. Glasgow, Al Rose, and Diana Beals Rose, Draft, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript, "Louisiana's Singing Century: One Hundred Years of Popular Culture Mirrored in Music," Vaughn L. Glasgow, Al Rose, and Diana Beals Rose, Draft, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript, "Louisiana's Singing Century: One Hundred Years of Popular Culture Mirrored in Music," Vaughn L. Glasgow, Al Rose, and Diana Beals Rose, Draft, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript, "Louisiana's Singing Century: One Hundred Years of Popular Culture Mirrored in Music," Vaughn L. Glasgow, Al Rose, and Diana Beals Rose, Notes, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript, "Louisiana's Singing Century: One Hundred Years of Popular Culture Mirrored in Music," Vaughn L. Glasgow, Al Rose, and Diana Beals Rose, Notes, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript, "Louisiana's Singing Century: One Hundred Years of Popular Culture Mirrored in Music," Vaughn L. Glasgow, Al Rose, and Diana Beals Rose, Notes, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript, "Louisiana's Singing Century: One Hundred Years of Popular Culture Mirrored in Music," Vaughn L. Glasgow, Al Rose, and Diana Beals Rose, Notes, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Obituary, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Photograph, Ferdinand "Jelly Roll" Morton, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, Squibb and William Russell, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Early Jazz Musicians, circa 1900s-1910s (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Program, "Eubie!," circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Report, Estate of Margaret E. Penney, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Series II: Catalogs, Discographies, and Publications
  - 78 Quarterly, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - "Al Rose's Sheet Music List," undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Australian Jazz Quarterly, 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Beauty and the Beast," 1896 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Big Book of Swing, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Black and White, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Brunswick Collectors' Series, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Clef, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Climax, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Coda, 1963-1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Columbia Networks Catalog, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Down Beat, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Down Beat, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Down Beat, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Folk, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Giants of Jazz: Louis Armstrong, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "HiFi & Music Review," 1958 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Index of Jazz, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Index of Jazz, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - International Jazz Collector's Directory, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Jazz, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Jazz and Pop, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Jazz Appreciation Society Booklet, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Jazz Discography, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Jazz Folio, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Jazz Information, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Jazz Journal, 1948-1951 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Jazz Journal, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Jazz Journal, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Jazz Journal, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Jazz Journal, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Jazz Journal, 1959-1965 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Jazz Monthly, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Jazz Music, 1946-1948 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Jazz Report, 1957-1965 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - The Jazz Review, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Jazz World, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Jazzology, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - The Long Player, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Matrix, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - The Metronome Yearbook, 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Music Memories and Jazz Report, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - The Needle: Record Collector's Guide, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Ragtimer," 1967 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - "Record Information," undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Record Research, 1958-1968 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Revues des Disques, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "Schwann: Artist Issue," 1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Sounds and Fury, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Theme, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Universal Jazz, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Series III: Printed and Handwritten Music
  - Art Tatum, "5 Jazz Piano Solos by Art Tatum," transcribed by Frank Paparelli; Leeds Music Corporation, 1944 "5 Jazz Piano Solos by Art Tatum," transcribed by Frank Paparelli; Leeds Music Corporation, 1944 "Art Tatum Improvisations No. 1," Robbins Music Corporation, 1939 "Art Tatum Improvisations No. 1," Robbins Music Corporation, 1939 "Art Tatum Improvisations No. 2," Robbins Music Corporation, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Bob Zurke, "At the Jazz Band Ball," D. LaRocca and Larry Shields, arranged by Bob Zurke; Leo Feist, Inc., 1939 "At the Jazz Band Ball," D. LaRocca and Larry Shields, arranged by Bob Zurke; Leo Feist, Inc., 1939 "Dog Town Blues," Bob Haggart, arranged by Bob Zurke; Leo Feist, Inc., 1939 "Gin Mill Blues," Joe Sullivan, arranged by Bob Zurke; Leo Feist, Inc., 1939 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Bop Books, "The Be-Bop Style," Van Alexander; Criterion Music Corporation, 1949 "Billy Taylor's Basis Be-Bop Instruction," Chas. H. Hansen Music, 1949 "Errol Garner: Five Original Piano Solos," transcribed by Morris Feldman; Capitol Songs, 1950 "How to Play Modern Jazz," Walter Stuart; Charles Colin, 1958 "Modern Jazz Piano Solos," Billy Taylor; Chas. H. Hansen Music, 1953 "Modern Jazz Piano Solos," Billy Taylor; Soundpost, Inc., 1959 "Touch of Taylor," Billy Taylor; Chas. H. Hansen Music, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Clarence "Pine-Top" Smith, "5 Original Compositions by Pine Tope Smith," transcribed by Frank Paparelli; Leeds Music Corporation, 1941 "The Original Boogie Woogie," Melrose Music Corporation, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Fake Books, "Blues in E Flat," Red Norvo and Irving Mills, 1935 "Dixieland Band Book," Philip J. Lang, 1953 "Ja-Da," Bob Carleton, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Ferdinand "Jelly Roll" Morton, "Big Fat Ham," arranged J. Lawrence Cook; Roy J. Carew, 1956 "Billy Goat Stomp," arranged by Tiny Parham, 1927 "Buddy Bolden's Blues (I Though I Heard Buddy Bolden Say)," transcribed by J. Lawrence Cook; Tempo-Music, 1950 "The Crave," transcribed by J. Lawrence Cook; Tempo-Music Publishing Company, 1950 "The Crave," transcribed by J. Lawrence Cook; Tempo-Music Publishing Company, 1950 "Finger Buster," Dunlap Printing Co., undated "Finger Buster," Dunlap Printing Co., undated "Finger Buster," Dunlap Printing Co., undated "Frog-i-more Rag," edited by J. Lawrence Cook; Roy J. Carew, 1946 "Frog-i-more Rag," edited by J. Lawrence Cook; Roy J. Carew, 1946 "Frog-i-more Rag," edited by J. Lawrence Cook; Roy J. Carew, 1946 "Grandpa's Spells," Melrose Bros., 1925 "Hyena Stomp," arranged by Elmer Schoebel; Melrose Bros., 1927 "If You Knew (How I Love You)," lyrics by Ed. Werac; Tempo-Music, 1938 "If You Knew (How I Love You)," lyrics by Ed. Werac; Tempo-Music, 1938 "'Jelly Roll' Morton's Famous Series of Blues & Stomps, Book 1," Herman Darewski Music Publishing Company, 1923 "'Jelly Roll' Morton's Famous Series of Blues & Stomps, Book 1," Herman Darewski Music Publishing Company, 1923 "'Jelly Roll' Morton's Famous Series of Blues & Stomps, Book 2," Herman Darewski Music Publishing Company, 1927 "'Jelly Roll' Morton's Famous Series of Blues & Stomps, Book 3," Herman Darewski Music Publishing Company, 1951 "'Jelly Roll' Morton's Famous Series of Blues & Stomps, Book 3," Herman Darewski Music Publishing Company, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Ferdinand "Jelly Roll" Morton, "'Jelly Roll' Morton's Folio," edited by George Hoefer; Melrose Music Corporation, 1949 "'Jelly Roll' Morton's Folio," edited by George Hoefer; Melrose Music Corporation, 1949 "Jungle Blues," arranged by Chas. E. Cooke; Melrose Bros., 1928 "Kansas City Stomps," Melrose Bros., 1925 "King Porter Stomp," Melrose Music Corporation, 1925 "King Porter Stomp," Melrose Music Corporation, 1925 "King Porter Stomp," Melrose Music Corporation, 1925 "Mamie's Blues," transcribed by J. Lawrence Cook; Tempo-Music, 1948 "Millenberg Joys," Walter Melrose, music by Leon Roppolo-Paul Mares and "Jelly Roll" Morton; Melrose Bros., 1925 "The Miserere," transcribed by J. Lawrence Cook; Roy J. Carew, 1949 "The Miserere," transcribed by J. Lawrence Cook; Roy J. Carew, 1949 "The Miserere," transcribed by J. Lawrence Cook; Roy J. Carew, 1949 "My Home is in a Southern Town," Tempo-Music, 1938 "The Naked Dance," transcribed by J. Lawrence Cook; Tempo-Music, 1950 "The Naked Dance," transcribed by J. Lawrence Cook; Tempo-Music, 1950 "The Pearls," transcribed by Dick Hyman; Edwin H. Morris & Company, 1925 "Sidewalk Blues," Walter Melrose, music by Jelly Roll Morton; Melrose Bros., 1927 "Smart Set Stomp," Harrison Smith, 1946 "Sweet Substitute," Tempo-Music, 1938 "Sweeheart O' Mine," Walter Melrose, music by Jelly Roll Morton; Melrose Bros., 1926 "Sweeheart O' Mine," Walter Melrose, music by Jelly Roll Morton; Melrose Bros., 1926 "Sweeheart O' Mine," Walter Melrose, music by Jelly Roll Morton; Melrose Bros., 1926 "We Are Elks," Ed Werac, music by Jelly Roll Morton; Tempo-Music, 1939 "We Are Elks," Ed Werac, music by Jelly Roll Morton; Tempo-Music, 1939 "Winin' Boy Blues," transcribed by J. Lawrence Cook; Tempo-Music, 1950 "Why," Ed Werac, music by Jelly Roll Morton; Tempo-Music, 1938 "Wild Man Blues," arranged Tiny Parham; Melrose Bros., 1927 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Handwritten Music, "Brittwood Rag," Eubie Blake, 1959 "Cleopatra Rag," Lamb, undated "Champagne Rag," Lamb, undated "Charleston Rag," Eubie Blake, undated "Eubie Boogie Rag," Eubie Blake, 1959 "Love Made a Fool out of Me," C.A. Burton, 1958 Manuscript Book, undated "Mean Women," arranged by Buck Clayton, undated Music Transcriptions, 1971 Music Transcriptions, undated "Riff Example," Ferdinand "Jelly Roll" Morton, 1948 "Rumpus Rag," Don Ewell, undated "Squibb Scramble," Don Ewell, 1950 Unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - James P. Johnson, "Blues For Fats," Mills Music, Inc., 1948 "The Carolina Shout," Clarence Williams Music Publishing Company, 1926 "The Carolina Shout," Clarence Williams Music Publishing Company, 1926 "Dixieland Echoes," Perry Bradford and James P. Johnson; Perry Bradford, Inc., 1928 "Ebony Dreams," Perry Bradford, Inc., 1928 "James Johnson's Piano Jazzfest," Bregman, Vocco, and Conn, Inc., 1946 "Jazzapation," Perry Bradford, Inc., 1927 "Jimmy Johnson's Boogie Woogie," Mills Music, Inc., 1943 "Jingles," Clarence Williams Music Publishing Company, 1926 "Keep off the Grass," Clarence Williams Music Publishing Company, 1926 "Modernistic," Clarence Williams Music Publishing Company, 1933 "Piano Solos by James P. Johnson," Clarence Williams Music Publishing Company, 1945 "Scalin' the Blues," Clarence Williams Music Publishing Company, 1926 "Yamekraw," Perry Bradford, Inc., 1927 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - James Scott, "Broadway Rag," Stark Music Co., 1922 "Climax Rag," Melrose Brothers Music Company, 1914 "Evergreen Rag," Melrose Brothers Music Company, 1915 "Frog Legs Rag," Stark Music Co., 1906 "Frog Legs Rag," Stark Music Co., 1906 "Grace and Beauty," Melrose Music Corporation, 1937 "Grace and Beauty," Melrose Music Corporation, 1937 "Hilarity Rag," Melrose Brothers Music Company, 1910 "Honey Moon Rag," Melrose Brothers Music Company, 1916 "Kansas City Rag," Stark Music Co., 1907 "Prosperity Rag," Melrose Brothers Music Company, 1916 "Quality Rag," Melrose Brothers Music Company, 1911 "Ragtime Oriole," Melrose Brothers Music Company, 1911 "Victory Rag," Stark Music Co., 1921 "Victory Rag," Melrose Brothers Music Company, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Jess Stacy, "Ain't Goin' Nowhere," Bregman, Vocco, and Conn Inc., 1939 "Eager Beaver," Stan Kenton, arranged by Jess Stacy; Robbins Music Corporation, 1945 "Two O'Clock Jump," Harry James, Count Basie, and Benny Goodman, arranged by Jess Stacy; Robbins Music Corporation, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Jim Yancey, "5 Boogie Woogie and Blues Piano Solos," Leeds Music Corporation, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Joe Sullivan, "Blues and Barrel-House Piano Solos," Robbins Music Corporation, 1945 "Little Rock Getaway," arranged by Bob Zurke; Leo Feist, Inc., 1939 "Little Rock Getaway," arranged by Bob Zurke; Leo Feist, Inc., 1939 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Kunkel's Musical Review, 1894-1898 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Meade "Lux" Lewis, "5 Boogie Woogie Piano Solos by Meade 'Lux' Lewis," Leeds Music Corporation, 1941 "5 Boogie Woogie Piano Solos by Meade 'Lux' Lewis," Leeds Music Corporation, 1941 "5 Boogie Woogie Piano Solos by Meade 'Lux' Lewis," Leeds Music Corporation, 1941 "Yancey Special," Shapiro, Bernstein & Company, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Method Books, "Axel Christensen's Rag-time Instruction Book for Piano," 1909 "Axel Christensen's Rag Time Instructor, No. 2," 1909 "Axel Christensen's Rag Time Instructor, No. 2," 1909 "Axel Christensen's Rag Time Instructor, No. 2," 1909 "Axel Christensen's Rag Time Instructor, No. 2," 1909 "Axel Christensen's Instruction Book for Jazz and Novelty Piano Playing," 1927 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Method Books, "The Elements of Piano Technique," Ernest Hutcheson, 1907 "Foundation to Cornet Playing: An Elementary Method," Edwin Franko Goldman, 1914 "Jazz Technique," 1924 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Method Books, "Studies in Counterpoint," Ernst Křenek, 1940 "Six Blues-Roots Pianists," Eric Kriss, 1973 "Vincent Lopez Modern Piano Method," 1934 "Winn's How to Play Ragtime (Uneven Rhythm), Book 2," 1942 "Winn's How to Play Ragtime (Uneven Rhythm), Book 2," 1942 "Winn's How to Play Jazz and Blues, Book 3," 1920 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Photocopied Music, 1905-1940 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Scott Joplin, "Antoninette," Stark Music Printing, 1906 "The Cascades," Melrose Bros., 1904 "The Chrysanthemum," John Stark & Son, 1904 "Country Club," Mills Music, 1909 "The Easy Winners," Stark Music Company, 1901 "Elite Syncopations," John Stark & Son, 1902 "Eugenia," Will Rossiter, 1905 "Euphonic Sounds," Mills Music, 1909 "The Favorite," A.W. Perry's Sons, 1904 "The Favorite," A.W. Perry's Sons, 1904 "The Favorite," A.W. Perry's Sons, 1904 "Gladiolus Rag," Edw. B. Marks Music Company, 1921 "Magnetic Rag," undated "Maple Leaf Rag," John Stark & Son, 1899 "Maple Leaf Rag," John Stark & Son, 1899 "Maple Leaf Rag," Melrose Music Corporation, 1939 "March Majestic," John Stark & Son, 1902 "March Majestic," John Stark & Son, 1902 "Original Rags," arranged by Chas. N. Daniels; Jerome H. Remick & Co., 1903 "Paragon Rag," Mills Music, 1938 "Rosebud," John Stark & Son, 1905 "Rosebud," John Stark & Son, 1905 "Search-Light Rag," Edward B. Marks Music Corporation, 1935 "Scott Joplin's New Rag," Edward B. Marks Music Corporation, 1940 "Scott Joplin's World's Famous Jazz Classics for Piano," Stark Music Co., undated "Sugar Cane," Mills Music, 1938 "Sunflower Slow Drag," John Stark & Son, 1901 "Swipsy," Stark Music Co., 1900 "The Sycamore," 1910 "Weeping Willow," Mills Music,1903 "Weeping Willow," Mills Music,1903 (Box 13, Folder 3)